In this and the next
在现在及未来
(字幕整理：中国海洋大学 黄海广,haiguang2000@qq.com )
few videos, I want to
一些视频，我想
start to talk about classification problems,
开始谈论的分类问题，
where the variable y that
其中变量y表示
you want to predict is discreet
要预测是谨慎的
valued. We'll develop an
估值。我们将开发一个
algorithm called logistic regression,
算法称为Logistic回归，
which is one of the
这是一个
most popular and most widely used learning algorithms today.
最流行，最广泛使用的今天学习算法。
Here are some examples of classification problems.
下面是分类问题的一些例子。
Earlier, we talked about emails,
此前，我们谈到了电子邮件，
spam classification as an
垃圾分类作为
example of a classification problem.
例的分类问题。
Another example would be classifying online transactions.
另一个例子是分类网上交易。
So, if you have a website
所以，如果你有一个网站
that sells stuff and if you
卖的东西，如果你
want to know if a physical
要知道，如果一个物理
transaction is fraudulent or
交易是欺诈或
not, whether someone has, you
不，某人是否有你
know, is using a stolen credit card
知道，是用偷来的信用卡
or has stolen the user's password.
或窃取用户的密码。
That's another classification problem, and
这是另一种分类问题，
earlier we also talked about
我们前面也谈到了
the example of classifying tumors
瘤进行分类的例子
as a cancerous malignant or as benign tumors.
作为恶性癌或良性肿瘤。
In all of these problems,
在所有的这些问题，
the variable that we're trying
我们正在努力变
to predict is a variable
预测是一个可变
Y that we can think
y表示我们可以认为
of as taking on two values,
作为取两个值，
either zero or one, either
为零或1，或者
a spam or not spam, fraudulent
垃圾邮件或者非垃圾邮件，欺诈性
or not fraudulent, malignant or benign.
或不欺诈，恶性或良性。
Another name for the class
该类的另一个名字
that we denote with 0 is
我们表示具有0
the negative class, and another
负类，和另一
name for the class that we
命名的类，我们
denote with 1 is the positive class.
表示与图1是阳性的类。
So 0 may denote the
所以，0可以表示
benign tumor and 1
良性肿瘤和1
positive class may denote a malignant tumor.
阳性类可表示的恶性肿瘤。
The assignment of the 2
的2的分配
classes, you know, spam,
类，你知道，垃圾邮件，
no spam, and so on -
没有垃圾邮件，等等 -
the assignment of the 2
的2的分配
classes to positive and negative,
类，以积极和消极的，
to 0 and 1 is somewhat
为0和1是有点
arbitrary and it doesn't really matter.
任意的，它其实并不重要。
But often there is this
但往往有这样的
intuition that the negative
直觉，负
class is conveying the
类输送
absence of something, like the absence
缺少的东西，就像没有
of a malignant tumor, whereas one,
的恶性肿瘤，而之一，
the positive class, is conveying
正班，被输送
the presence of something that we may be looking for.
的东西，我们可能会寻找存在。
But the definition of which
但它的定义
is negative and which is positive
是负的，这是正
is somewhat arbitrary and it doesn't matter that much.
是任意的，这一点并不重要得多。
For now, we're going to start
现在，我们要开始
with classification problems with just
与分类问题，只需
two classes; zero and one.
两班;零和1。
Later on, we'll talk about multi-class
稍后，我们将讨论多级
problems as well, whether variable
问题还有，是否变
Y may take on say,
Y可以采取的发言权，
for value zero, one, two and three.
对值零，一，二，三。
This is called a multi-class classification problem,
这就是所谓的多类分类问题，
but for the next few
但在未来数
videos, let's start with the
视频，让我们先从
two class or the binary classification problem.
二级或二元分类问题。
and we'll worry about the multi-class setting later.
我们稍后会担心多类设置。
So, how do we develop a classification algorithm?
那么，我们如何建立一个分类算法？
Here's an example of a
下面是一个例子
training set for a classification
对于分类训练集
task for classifying a tumor
任务的肿瘤分类
as malignant or benign and
为恶性或良性，
notice that malignancy takes on
注意到恶性肿瘤发生在
only two values zero or
只有两个值为零或
no or one or one or yes.
没有或一个或一个或肯定。
So, one thing we could
所以，有一件事我们可以
do given this training set
不要给这个训练集
is to apply the algorithm
是应用该算法
that we already know, linear regression to this data set
我们已经知道，线性回归，这组数据
and just try to fit the straight line to the data.
而只是尝试，以适应直线的数据。
So, if you take this training
所以，如果你把这个培训
set and fill a straight
设置和填充直
line to it, maybe you get
行吧，也许你会得到
hypothesis that looks like that.
假设，看起来像这样。
Alright, so that's my hypothesis, h of
好了，所以这是我的假设，H的
x equals theta transpose
x等于西塔转
x. If you want
按x。  如果你想
to make predictions, one thing
作出预测，一件事
you could try doing is then
你可以尝试做的是那么
threshold the classifier outputs at 0.5.
阈值分类器输出为0.5。
That is at the vertical access value 0.5.
即在垂直通道值0.5。
And if the hypothesis outputs
并且，如果假设输出
a value that's greater than
一个值，该值是大于
equal to 0.5 you predict y equals one.
等于0.5您预测y等于之一。
If it's less than 0.5, you predict y equals zero.
如果它小于0.5，你预测y等于为零。
Let's see what happens when we do that.
让我们来看看，当我们这样做会发生什么。
So, let's take 0.5, and
所以，让我们取0.5，和
so, you know, that's where the threshold is.
所以，你知道，这就是门槛。
And thus, using linear regression this way.
因此，使用线性回归这种方式。
Everything to the right
一切的权利
of this point, we will end
这一点，我们将结束
up predicting as the positive
向上预测作为正
class because of the output
因为输出级
values are greater than 0.5
值大于0.5
on the vertical axis and
在垂直轴上，并
everything to the left
一切向左侧
of that point we will end
这一点，我们将结束
up predicting as a negative value.
向上预测为负值。
In this particular example, it
在这个特定的例子中，它
looks like linear regression is actually
看起来像线性回归实际上是
doing something reasonable even though
做的事情，即使合理
this is a classification task we're
这是一个分类的任务我们
interested in.
感兴趣。
But now let's try changing problem a bit.
但现在让我们尝试改变的问题了一下。
Let me extend out the horizontal
让我伸出水平
axis of orbit and let's
轨道的轴，让我们
say we got one more training
说我们得到了一个更多的培训
example way out there on the right.
例如出路在那里就对了。
Notice that that additional training
请注意，这额外的培训
example, this one out
例如，这一个了
here, it doesn't actually change anything, right?
在这里，它实际上并没有改变什么，对不对？
Looking at the training set, it
看着训练集，它
is pretty clear what a good hypothesis is.
是相当清楚什么是好的假设是。
Well, everything to the right of
好了，一切的权利
somewhere around here to the
某处在这里的
right of this we should predict
权这一点，我们应该预测
as positive, and everything to
为阳性，什么都
the left we should probably predict
左边，我们也许应该预测
as negative because from this
因为从这个负
training set it looks like
培训设置它看起来像
all the tumors larger than, you
所有比你大的肿瘤
know, a certain value around here
知道了，在这里一定值
are malignant, and all the
是恶性的，并且所有的
tumors smaller than that are
肿瘤比那些小
not malignant, at least for this training set.
不是恶性的，至少在这个训练集。
But once we've added
但是我们增加一次
that extra example out here,
额外的例子在这里，
if you now run linear regression,
如果你现在运行的线性回归，
you instead get a straight line fit to the data.
你不是得到一条直线拟合数据。
That might maybe look like this, and
这可能也许是这样的，和
if you now threshold this hypothesis
如果你现在这个门槛假说
at 0.5, you end up with
0.5，你结束了
a threshold that's around here
一个阈值是在这里
so that everything to the right
所以，一切的权利
of this point you predict as
这一点，您预测为
positive, and everything to the left of that point you predict as negative.
积极的，一切到该点的左边你预测为阴性。
And this seems a pretty
而这似乎是一个相当
bad thing for linear regression to have done, right?
坏事线性回归，都做了，对吧？
Because, you know, these are
因为，你知道，这些都是
our positive examples, these are our negative examples.
我们积极的例子，这些都是我们的负面的例子。
It's pretty clear, we should
这是很清楚的，我们应该
really be separating the two classes
真正分开两班
somewhere around there, but somehow
我身边不远，但不知何故
by adding one example way
通过添加一个实例方式
out here to the right, this
这里的权利，这
example really isn't giving us any new information.
例如还真是不给我们任何新的信息。
I mean, it should be no
我的意思是，应该没
surprise to the learning out of
惊喜地学习出
that the example way out here turns out to be malignant.
那这里的例子的方式原来是恶性的。
But somehow adding that example
但不知何故，并称例子
out there caused linear regression
在那里引起的线性回归
to change in straight line fit
在直线拟合改变
to the data from this
从这个数据
magenta line out here
洋红色线条在这里
to this blue line over here,
这个蓝线在这里，
and caused it to give us a worse hypothesis.
而造成它给我们一个更坏的假设。
So, applying linear regression
因此，应用线性回归
to a classification problem usually
一个分类问题通常
isn't, often isn't a great idea.
是不是，往往不是一个好主意。
In the first instance, in the
在一审中，
first example before I added
之前，第一个例子我添加
this extra training example,
这个额外的培训为例，
previously linear regression was
此前线性回归是
just getting lucky and it
刚开幸运，它
got us a hypothesis that, you
我们得到了一个假设，你
know, worked well for that particular
知道的，运作良好，对特定
example, but usually apply
例如，但通常适用
linear regression to a data set,
线性回归到一个数据集，
you know, you might get lucky but
你知道，你可能会得到幸运，但
often it isn't a good
通常它不是一个好
idea, so I wouldn't use
的想法，所以我不会用
linear regression for classification problems.
对于分类问题线性回归。
Here is one other funny thing
这里是另外一个有趣的事情
about what would happen if
会发生什么，如果
we were to use linear regression for a classification problem.
我们用线性回归的分类问题。
For classification, we know that
对于分类，我们知道，
Y is either zero or one,
Y是0或1，
but if you are using
但如果您使用的是
linear regression, well the hypothesis
线性回归，以及假设
can output values much larger
可输出值大得多
than one or less than
大于1或小于
zero, even if all
零，即使所有
of good the training examples have labels
良好的训练样例有标签
Y equals zero or one,
Y等于0或1，
and it seems kind of strange
这似乎有点怪
that even though we
即使我们
know that the label should
知道标签应
be zero one, it seems
为零1，似乎
kind of strange if the
有点怪，如果
algorithm can offer values much
算法可以提供多少价值
larger than one or much smaller than zero.
比1大或大于零小得多。
So what we'll do in the
所以，我们会做的
next few videos is develop
接下来的几个视频是发展
an algorithm called logistic regression
所谓逻辑回归算法
which has the property that the
它具有属性的
output, the predictions of logistic
输出，物流的预测
regression are always between zero
回归总是零之间
and one, and doesn't become
和1，并不会成为
bigger than one or become less
大于1或变得不
than zero and by
大于零并通过
the way, logistic regression is
顺便说一下，logistic回归是
and we will use it as
我们将使用它作为
a classification algorithm in some,
的分类算法在某些，
maybe sometimes confusing that
也许有时混淆了
the term regression appears in
术语回归出现在
his name, even though logistic regression
他的名字，即使logistic回归
is actually a classification algorithm.
实际上是一种分类算法。
But that's just the name it
但是，这仅仅是它的名字
was given for historical reasons so don't be confused by that.
被赋予历史的原因，所以不要被迷惑了。
Logistic Regression is actually a
Logistic回归实际上是一种
classification algorithm that we
分类算法，我们
apply to settings where the
适用于设置在哪里
label Y is discreet valued. The 1001.
标签Y被谨慎的重视。 1001。
So hopefully you now
所以希望你现在
know why if you
知道是什么原因，如果你
have a causation problem using
使用有因果关系问题
linear regression isn't a good idea .
线性回归是不是一个好主意。
In the next video we'll
在接下来的视频中，我们将
start working out the details
开始制定细节
of the logistic regression algorithm.
的logistic回归算法。